

Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Full Stack Front-End Development



Current Designation: Senior Systems Engineer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Current Location: Nagpur

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Nagpur, Pune
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Development, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, Core Java, Node. Js, C#, Front End

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Driven and appreciated software engineer with 2 years of industry experience in developing front-end and backend software solutions. Seeking a development position to create solutions that make a difference. An articulate communicator, proactively undertook work to deliver successful sprints; acquired new skills and completed tasks with short deadlines successfully. Researched and provided insights into Machine Learning/NLP approaches, OCR technology, Semantic web, Azure Cognitive Services to enhance performance of data extraction and management tools.

Work Experience

Infosys as Senior Systems Engineer Dec 2020 to Till Date

L&T Technology Services as Engineer - IT Aug 2018 to Aug 2020

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from YeshwantRao Chavan College of Engineering, Nagpur in 2018

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Machine Learning -- Online Certification

Java -- Certification

Javascript Essential Training

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
HTML5	5	2020	2 Year(s)	
css3	3	2020	2 Year(s)	
JavaScript		2020	2 Year(s)	
Core Java (Certified)		2019	1 Year(s)	
C#		2020	0 Year(s) 8 Month(s)	
ASP.NET Web API		2020	0 Year(s) 8 Month(s)	
ASP.Net MVC		2020	0 Year(s) 8 Month(s)	
AngularJs		2019	0 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
Python		2020		
SQL		2020		
TORTOISESVN		2020		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - non-creamy

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time